<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Ragone</title>
    <link>https://davidragone.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Ragone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 18:31:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidragone.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Write Comments In Your Code</title>
      <link>https://davidragone.com/blog/why-you-should-write-comments-in-your-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 18:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidragone.com/blog/why-you-should-write-comments-in-your-code/</guid>
      <description>Why you should write comments in your code Aka, self-documenting code and other programming myths. Especially in the ruby community, there&amp;rsquo;s a strong animosity to commenting or documenting code. The usual retort is something to the effect of &amp;ldquo;comments are future lies&amp;rdquo;, referencing how they can easily become an incorrect representation of what the code does.
In my experience, this both ignores an important aspect of the job, and misstates the purpose of comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Multiple Themes With Hugo</title>
      <link>https://davidragone.com/blog/using-multiple-themes-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 08:05:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidragone.com/blog/using-multiple-themes-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I like the simplicity of the first theme I chose for this site, hugo-sustain. After setting it up, however, I realized that the &amp;ldquo;resume&amp;rdquo; section links to a separate site, and actually uses a different theme (hugo-vitae). I wanted to be able to use two hugo themes on the same site, and spent a little time investigating how to do that.
There&amp;rsquo;s essentially two options (as with anything in programming, there&amp;rsquo;s tradeoffs in where you put the complexity):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balance</title>
      <link>https://davidragone.com/blog/balance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 06:43:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidragone.com/blog/balance/</guid>
      <description>An ad from Apple has some interesting ideas on how to live life:
Pathetic… even Apple is promoting workaholism now. Check out this ad for their Planet Of The Apps show. pic.twitter.com/PKn30pWWgn
&amp;mdash; Jason Fried (@jasonfried) June 9, 2017  I suppose I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised seeing such things from Apple (the company building a campus with everything but a daycare), but I still can&amp;rsquo;t believe this ad. It reminds me of an interesting discussion I had with a former manager about what and how we celebrate wins, and how that defines our culture and norms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://davidragone.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidragone.com/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>